export const catalog = [
    {question: "The highest mountain in South America is the... ",
    answers: ["Aconcagua", "Ojos del Salado", "Monte Pissis"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "Tsutomu Yamaguchi became famous for what?",
    answers: ["He was the first climber of Mount Fuji", "He survived two atomic bomb drops", "He is the oldest documented man in the world "],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "How many times does the earth fit into the sun?",
    answers: ["About 560 thousand times", "About 1.3 million times","About 2.3 million times"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "Who was kidnapped during a broadcast in South Africa in 2005?",
    answers: ["Matt Damon", "Robert De Niro", "Benedict Cumberbatch"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "Who is related to Abraham Lincoln?",
    answers: ["Bruce Springsteen", "Stephen King", "Tom Hanks"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "Which US president was the first to be born in the 20th century?",
    answers: ["Lyndon B. Johnson", "John F. Kennedy", "Richard M. Nixon"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "What was done in honor of Alexander Graham Bell after his death?",
    answers: ["All telephones in Canada and the USA were switched off for one minute", "His personal telephone was installed in the Oval Office", "His tombstone is modeled after a telephone fork"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "What helped Roy Sullivan achieve world fame?",
    answers: ["He predicted the September 11 attacks", "He was the first to fly across the English Channel", "He was struck by lightning seven times"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "What already existed in ancient Rome?",
    answers: ["Parking signs", "Swivel chairs", "Heated bathroom mirrors"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "Until 1914 in the United States you were allowed to...",
    answers: ["Marry your handgun", "Take cows to work", "Send children via mail"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "What makes the year 1315 so special in Europe?",
    answers: ["It is the only year without a documented murder", "It rains in large parts for 8 months at a stretch", "7 times more children were born than in the previous year"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "In 1945 a german submarine sank because the captain...",
    answers: ["rammed a fishing boat while drunk", "Operated a wrong valve on the toilet", "Smoked in the ammunition room"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "In 1859...",
    answers: ["One could see auroras in Rome", "There were the most wars in the history of mankind", "Milk was banned as a food in France"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "What made the army of Liechtenstein famous in 1866?",
    answers: ["A sheep was deputy commander", "The commander adopted his entire army", "More men came back than before the war"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "The seven wonders of the ancient world... ",
    answers: ["Existed only 60 years at the same time", "Used more concrete than all of Manhattan today", "Weighed more together than Pluto"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "In 1958 disappeared...",
    answers: ["The Mexican president for 10 months because he needed a vacation", "An atomic bomb from the US arsenal, which is still considered missing today", "One fifth of Spanish gold, the biggest financial loss of all time"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "Singapore is the only country in the world that...",
    answers: ["Involuntarily became independent", "Did without prisons for decades", "Excluded professional politicians from elections"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "Why do women traditionally stand to the left of the groom at a wedding ceremony?",
    answers: ["Since the gift table was on the right side and the women had no right to it", "Since many churches had an emergency exit on the left side", "So that the man could defend the woman with his right hand on the sword"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "In the Middle Ages...",
    answers: ["Green was the color of love", "You shook hands with the left hand", "Shamrocks stood for bad luck"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "Every time before Beethoven composed, he...",
    answers: ["Dipped his head into cold water", "Stubbed his toes on the piano", "Was lying down under the piano for 2 minutes"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "King Alfonso of Spain (1886-1931)...",
    answers: ["Could only speak Portuguese", "Could not recognize the Spanish national anthem", "Never used peseta as a currency"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "The Netherlands... ",
    answers: ["Have the longest family monarchy in the world", "Have no official language", "Have the oldest national anthem in the world"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "The Kinkajou (or honey bear) can...",
    answers: ["Go up to a month without sleep", "Eat 5 times their body weight", "Run backwards just as fast as they can run forwards"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "Most sloths die...",
    answers: ["While going to the toilet", "While breeding", "While sleeping"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "Manatees use...",
    answers: ["Sea urchins as a weapon", "Flatulences to regulate their buoyancy", "Sea weeds as dental floss"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "The nerve cords in your body...",
    answers: ["Strung together, reach to the moon and back", "Would fit together in your little toe", "Could hold 5 tons of weight"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "0.5% of the earth's male population...",
    answers: ["Is infertile from birth", "Is lactose intolerant", "Is related to Dschinigs Khan"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "If you live in a floor apartment in Switzerland it is forbidden to...",
    answers: ["Flush the toilet after 10 pm", "Have a pillow fight on the weekend", "Wear high heels after midnight"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "Neil Harbisson has had an antenna implanted in his head to...",
    answers: ["Speak every language on Earth", "Hear colors", "See in the dark"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "In 1895 in the state of Ohio... ",
    answers: ["Triplets found themselves at a fair. They were separated at birth 31 years earlier", "There were only two cars on the road. They collided", "A guinea pig was declared the heraldic animal, although one never lived there"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "In 1979, President Jimmy Carter was attacked by a...",
    answers: ["Little blind elephant", "Flying angry squirrel", "Giant swimming rabbit"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "Roman Emperor Caligula ordered ten thousand soldiers to...",
    answers: ["Stab the sea with spears", "Clear the desert with buckets", "Cut down the Germanic forest with knives"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "The patent for the...",
    answers: ["Reading glasses is not readable", "Fire hydrate burned", "Document shredder was cut up"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "In 1976, the U.S. used an army of tanks, helicopters, B-52 bombers, special forces, Tae Kwon Do experts, and soldiers with grenade launchers to...",
    answers: ["Kill a rat", "Search for a stray dog", "Cut down a tree"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "During the First World War, Jean Navarre attacked a...",
    answers: ["Tank with a can opener", "Zeppelin with a kitchen knife", "Naval ship with a screwdriver"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "The most widespread disease in the world is...",
    answers: ["Dental caries", "Foot fungus", "Psoriasis"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "92% of all money in the world...", 
    answers: ["Came into contact with drugs", "Belongs to 0.01% of the richest people", "Does not physically exist"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "What was sold at auction for $2.7 million?", 
    answers: ["A cooking recipe", "A phone number", "An email-address"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "Half of the world's population has never...", 
    answers: ["Sent a letter", "Attended school", "Made a phone call"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "The surface area of your lungs is about the size of a...", 
    answers: ["Baseball field", "Tennis court", "Soccerfield"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "A human brain...", 
    answers: ["Generates more electrical impulses in a day than cell phones in the world", "Has more protein than 100.000 chicken eggs", "Makes up only 0.5% of the total weight of a person"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "The bird of paradise...", 
    answers: ["Has different colors every year", "Has more than 256 colors", "Absorbs 99.95% of the light"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "To get more food from their keepers, panda bears can...", 
    answers: ["Clean up their enclosure themselves", "Lower their weight for a short time at weigh-ins", "Fake pregnancy"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "The larvae of Leafhoppers (Magicicada)... ", 
    answers: ["Hatch after 17 years", "Can already reproduce", "Have neither brain nor heart"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "What was an Olympic discipline between 1912 and 1948? ", 
    answers: ["Fashion Design", "Architecture", "Literature"],
    correct: 1},
    {question: "In China, movies are banned if they show...", 
    answers: ["Horse riding", "Aliens", "Time travel"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "In Tennessee, women are legally allowed to drive only if...", 
    answers: ["Their father or husband is a driving instructor", "They wear a helmet while doing so", "A man walks in front waving a red flag"],
    correct: 2},
    {question: "According to legend, the Greek poet Aeschylus was killed in 456 BC by what?", 
    answers: ["By a falling turtle", "By a flying dolphin", "By a rolling bear"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "On Venus...", 
    answers: ["A day is longer than a year", "You only weigh a quarter", "You could run twice as fast as on Earth"],
    correct: 0},
    {question: "One ingredient of dynamite is...", 
    answers: ["Broccoli", "Peanuts", "Potatoes"],
    correct: 1},
]